# **SRILALITHA NOOKALA (SRI)**

Melbourne, Victoria, 3024

Phone: 0498800532| Email: srilalitha.ganti@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/srilalitha-nookala | GitHub: https://github.com/SrilalithaN | Portfolio: https://srilalithan.github.io/Portfolio/

#### Summary

A Full Stack Web Developer based in Melbourne with a technical background in Electronics and Communication engineering and life-long dedication to learning. Trained at Coding bootcamp and earned a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from Monash University. Effective at combining analytical problem-solving ability and apply critical thinking to design, build, test and deploy software solutions for a better customer experience. A passionate and self-motivated programmer with understanding of programming fundamentals and concepts and an aim to write clean code and architecting quality solutions with a passion for bringing others on the journey. A collaborative team player with effective time management skills, an enthusiastic person with excellent written and verbal communication skills and strong attention to detail. A quick learner, open to learn new technologies and frameworks.

#### **Technical Skills**

JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Express, ReactJs, NodeJS, Handlebars, jQuery, Bootstrap, REST APIs, GraphQI, Git.

#### **Projects**

# **Tracking-Journal**

https://annanguyen1.github.io/Track-Journal/homepage.html https://github.com/SrilalithaN/Track-Journal

- Tracking Journal is an application for users to find parks around a certain radius for a given address and keep track of their experiences.
- Responsibilities: To design one of the pages in the application, style it, display current weather by fetching Weather API, and some added functionalities to refine the III
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript/jQuery/ Web-APIs

#### Warehouse On Wheels

https://github.com/SrilalithaN/warehouse-manager https://warehouse-manager-bootcamp.herokuapp.com/

- Warehouse on Wheels is a Warehouse Management System for Second-hand car dealers. The owner/employee of the car dealership can login or Signup using their credentials and manage their inventory anywhere and anytime.
- Responsibilities: Managed the Routes part of the project that follows the MVC paradigm.

HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Node.js/ Express.js /Handlebars.js/ MySQL/Sequelize

#### **Patient Appointment booking System**

https://github.com/SrilalithaN/Patient-Appointment-BookingSystem https://mysterious-beach-71045.herokuapp.com/

- Patient Appointment booking system is a website for private clinic for private clinic with a feature to book appointments, view and cancel the appointments.
- Sole Contributor
- MERN Stack.

#### **Experience**

# Oxfam Volunteer Web Developer

Jan 2022 - Present Melbourne, Australia

- Review and update website using PHP, Laravel and Vue.js
- Worked on front-end to implement header and footer sections using bootstrap-Vue.

Sabbatical May 2018 - Jan 2022

- Relocated to Australia
- Family responsibilities
- Studied Udemy courses
- Volunteer for Toy Library

# Sree Vijaya Durga Junior College Junior Lecturer

December 2017- April 2018 Rajahmundry,

#### India

Volunteered as a Computer teacher for high-school students.

Key Accomplishments:

- Planning lessons and helping students gain theoretical and practical knowledge in computers.
- Ensuring wholesome development of students by developing their confidence in the subject.
- Managing the classroom, grading examinations/practical and guizzes
- Ensuring proper computer lab etiquettes are followed.
- Was a backup to the computer lab assistants and clerks for any computer-related help.

### **Education**

Certificate of Full Stack Web Development: Monash University. Melbourne, Victoria

**Bachelor Of Electronics and Communication Engineering:** L.D.R.P – Institute of Technology and Research. Gandhinagar, India.